be careful because Dallas announces
cuidado porque Dallas anuncia tercera
world war iii youtuber there are many people
guerra mundial youtuber hay mucha gente
who think and I think that's where the
que piensa y yo creo que van por ahí los
shots are going that the video is going for German I have
tiros que el vídeo va para Germán tengo
information about a certain garbage
información sobre cierta basura de
person that I have been
persona que llevo ya un tiempo
keeping from you for a while now I tell you once that it's
guardándote una vez ya os digo que se
coming strong and prepare for a few days
viene fuerte y preparados por unos días
of a lot of really strong hate prepared I only
de mucho hate fuertísimo preparados solo
tell you prepared it's going to be strong and there's
os digo preparados va a estar fuerte y
also another surprise video coming from
se viene además otro vídeo sorpresa de
a character that every time I talk
un personaje de que cada vez que hablo
about him I get a lot of hate but I'm going to
de él me cae mucho hate pero lo voy a
do it anyway I'm going to do it
hacer de todas maneras voy a hacer de
anyway because you're really going to
todas maneras porque vais de verdad a
freak out about what I found out and it
flipar de lo que me he enterado y pone
reveals once again that I was
al descubierto una vez más que yo tenía
right really and I tell you it's going to get a lot lot much much
razón de verdad y ya os digo va a caer
hate but a lot of
mucho mucho mucho mucho hate pero mucho
hate eh it's going to get but I'm going to do it
hate eh va a caer pero lo pienso hacer
Anyway I'm telling you that it's coming
De todas maneras ya os digo que se viene
strong and prepared for a few days that I
fuerte y preparado por unos días que que
say a lot lot much hatte Ah I don't know
diga mucho mucho mucho hatte Ah no sé
Herman no, people see him as
hermán no que la gente lo ve como
Untouchable
Intocable